{
  "courses": [
    {
      "title": "Basics 1",
      "slug": "Basics-1",
      "content": [
        {
          "question": "Ben",
          "choices": ["I", "You", "He", "She", "It"],
          "correctAnswer": 0,
          "id": "Basics-1-1"
        },
        {
          "question": "Sen",
          "choices": ["I am", "You", "He", "She", "It"],
          "correctAnswer": 1,
          "id": "Basics-1-2"
        },
        {
          "question": "Adam",
          "choices": ["Boy", "Woman", "Man", "Girl", "Son"],
          "correctAnswer": 2,
          "id": "Basics-1-3"
        },
        {
          "question": "Kadın",
          "choices": ["Boy", "Woman", "Man", "Girl", "Son"],
          "correctAnswer": 1,
          "id": "Basics-1-4"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Basics 2",
      "slug": "Basics-2",
      "content": [
        {
          "question": "Ben",
          "choices": ["I", "You", "He", "She", "It"],
          "correctAnswer": 0,
          "id": "Basics-2-1"
        },
        {
          "question": "Sen",
          "choices": ["I am", "You", "He", "She", "It"],
          "correctAnswer": 1,
          "id": "Basics-2-2"
        },
        {
          "question": "Adam",
          "choices": ["Boy", "Woman", "Man", "Girl", "Son"],
          "correctAnswer": 2,
          "id": "Basics-2-3"
        },
        {
          "question": "Kadın",
          "choices": ["Boy", "Woman", "Man", "Girl", "Son"],
          "correctAnswer": 1,
          "id": "Basics-2-4"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Fruits",
      "slug": "Fruits",
      "content": [
        {
          "question": "Apple",
          "choices": ["Armut", "Ananas", "Kiraz", "Elma", "Muz"],
          "correctAnswer": 3,
          "id": "Foods-1"
        },
        {
          "question": "Banana",
          "choices": ["Muz", "Kiraz", "Böğürtlen", "Ananas", "Armut"],
          "correctAnswer": 0,
          "id": "Foods-2"
        },
        {
          "question": "Strawberry",
          "choices": ["Kayısı", "Nane", "Ananas", "Armut", "Çilek"],
          "correctAnswer": 4,
          "id": "Foods-3"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
